http://www.recordinginstitute.com/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
Recording.Institute is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Recording.Institute site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Recording.Institute website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of Your Personal Information
There is information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Recording.Institute (hereinafter referred to as RID ). This information can include, but is not limited to: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by RID for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the RID website.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through RID public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others and is beyond the control of RID.
RID encourages you to review the privacy statements of web sites you choose to link to from RID so that you can understand how those web sites collect, use and share your information. RID is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on web sites outside of the RID and RID family of websites.
Use of your Personal Information
RID collects and uses your personal information to operate the RID website and deliver the services you have requested. RID also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from RID and its affiliates. RID may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
RID does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. RID may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.  In addition, RID may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, fulfill a subscription request, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to RID, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
RID does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent or where required by law.
RID keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within RID, in order to determine what RID services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within RID to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
RID web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on RID or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of RID; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of RID, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The RID site uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize RID pages, or register with RID site or services, a cookie helps RID to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same RID web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the RID features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the RID services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
RID secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. RID secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
RID will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. RID encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how RID is protecting your information.
Contact Information
RID welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that ALEX has not adhered to this Statement, please contact RID. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
© 2015 Recording.Institute. All Rights Reserved.
© Copyright 2015, The Recording Institute of Detroit, Inc. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
